Guide to the Bingham Center Women's Zine Collection, 1992-2017 RL.01406
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Bingham Center Women's Zine collection
1992-2017
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
RL.01406
2654
29 Linear Feet
This collection consists of zines, primarily authored by women, acquired as donations from multiple collectors or purchased from book stores, zine fairs, and zine distributors. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Collection Overview
This collection consists of zines, primarily authored by women, acquired as donations from multiple collectors or purchased from book stores, zine fairs, and zine distributors. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
- Accession (2006-0136), 1992-2006; 795759; 35 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  This collection consists of zines, primarily authored by women, acquired as donations from multiple collectors or purchased from book stores, zine fairs, and zine distributors. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
  - 3rd Annual Southern Girls Convention, 796621 (Box 1)
  - 4th Annual Southern Girls Convention, 796620 (Box 1)
  - 6x6, 796619 (Box 1)
  - 11th Street Ruse, 796618 (Box 1)
  - 20 Bus, 796617 (Box 1)
  - 21 Days Breaking the Habit, 796616 (Box 1)
  - 25 Things Zine, 796615 (Box 1)
  - 52 Weeks of Zines, 796614 (Box 1)
  - 90% Penguins, 796613 (Box 1)
  - 100 Jockeys, 796612 (Box 1)
  - 100% Natural Lull, 796611 (Box 1)
  - Abuse, 796610 (Box 1)
  - Abundance is Real, 796609 (Box 1)
  - Action Girl Newsletter, 796608 (Box 1)
  - Adorn, 796607 (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Ann Aurora, 796606 (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Anti-Career Girl, 796605 (Box 1)
  - The Adventures of Johnny Devine, 796604 (Box 1)
  - Aged Noise, 796603 (Box 1)
  - Alabama Grrrl, 796602 (Box 1)
  - Alice is an Island, 796601 (Box 1)
  - Alien Religion, 796600 (Box 1)
  - Allium, 796599 (Box 1)
  - Almost, 796598 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Bet, 796597 (Box 1)
  - Alphabet Zine, 796596 (Box 1)
  - Already Too Much; Never Enough, 796595 (Box 1)
  - American Girl, 796594 (Box 1)
  - Ancient, 796593 (Box 1)
  - The Anorexic Communist (Politically Incorrect) Gay Baby Harp Seal, 796592 (Box 1)
  - Anywhere I Lay My Head, 796591 (Box 2)
  - Apples Like Broken Glass/Decisive, 796590 (Box 2)
  - Applicant, 796589 (Box 2)
  - April Fools' Day, 796588 (Box 2)
  - Arroweb, 796587 (Box 2)
  - Arrowed, 796586 (Box 2)
  - The Artless Hymnal, 796585 (Box 2)
  - Art Seeds, 796584 (Box 2)
  - The Assassin and the Whiner, 796583 (Box 2)
  - At the Base of the Mountain Herstory, 796582 (Box 2)
  - Athena, 796581 (Box 2)
  - Aubade, 796580 (Box 2)
  - The Awkward Kid, 796579 (Box 2)
  - Awkward Spaces, 796578 (Box 2)
  - Ax Wound, 796577 (Box 2)
  - Axt Report, 796576 (Box 2)
  - Babydoll, 796575 (Box 2)
  - Baby Bloc, 796574 (Box 2)
  - Baby Girl (2 Folders), 796573 (Box 2)
  - Bad Breath, 796572 (Box 2)
  - Baltimore Co. Public Library Zine Collection, 796571 (Box 2)
  - Ballroom Etiquette, 796570 (Box 2)
  - Bamboo Girl, 796569 (Box 2)
  - Bamboo Girl, 796568 (Box 3)
  - Barefoot and in the Kitchen, 796567 (Box 3)
  - Barnard Zine Librarian Zine, 796566 (Box 3)
  - Bats with Baby Faces, 796565 (Box 3)
  - Battledore, 796564 (Box 3)
  - Beautiful Mess, 796563 (Box 3)
  - Beautiful Night, 796562 (Box 3)
  - Beauty is a Battlefield, 796561 (Box 3)
  - Being a Trans Alli Amonth Queer, Liberal, and Stubborn Friends, 796560 (Box 3)
  - Below Noon, 796559 (Box 3)
  - Ben is Sex, 796558 (Box 3)
  - Best Zine Ever!, 796557 (Box 3)
  - Beth's Zine, 796556 (Box 3)
  - Beyond, 796555 (Box 3)
  - Beyond Gallery Walls and Dead White Men, 796554 (Box 3)
  - Bicycle Threat, 796553 (Box 3)
  - Big Hate Ugly, 796552 (Box 3)
  - Big Ugly Red Monster Eyes, 796551 (Box 3)
  - Birlzine, 796550 (Box 3)
  - Birthdays and Christmas/Faking Distance, 796549 (Box 3)
  - Bitch, 796548 (Box 3)
  - Bitch King, 796547 (Box 3)
  - The Bitch Manifesto, 796546 (Box 3)
  - The Black-Eyed Peas, 796545 (Box 3)
  - The Blackheart Zine (2 Folders), 796544 (Box 3)
  - Black Mary, 796543 (Box 3)
  - Blank the Plague, 796542 (Box 3)
  - Blond on Blondes, 796541 (Box 3)
  - Blue, 796540 (Box 4)
  - Boa, 796539 (Box 4)
  - Body Count, 796538 (Box 4)
  - Bomb, 796537 (Box 4)
  - Bomb Shelter, 796536 (Box 4)
  - Borderlands, 796535 (Box 4)
  - Borderlands: It's a Family Affair, 796534 (Box 4)
  - Boredom Sucks, 796533 (Box 4)
  - Bound Struggles, 796532 (Box 4)
  - Brainscan (4 Folders), 796531 (Box 4)
  - Brat Attack: The Zine for Leatherdykes and Other Bad Girls, 796530 (Box 4)
  - Bratgirl, 796529 (Box 4)
  - Breakdancing for the Pope, 796528 (Box 4)
  - Brewster, 796527 (Box 4)
  - Bring the Pain, 796526 (Box 4)
  - Broken, 796525 (Box 4)
  - Broken Arrow, 796524 (Box 4)
  - Broken Hymen, 796523 (Box 4)
  - Broom, 796522 (Box 4)
  - Bulldozer, 796521 (Box 5)
  - Bunny Rabbit, 796520 (Box 5)
  - Burnside Landing, 796519 (Box 5)
  - Bus, 796518 (Box 5)
  - Cabinet of Curiosity, 796517 (Box 5)
  - Cadillac Girl, 796516 (Box 5)
  - Candy-Ass, 796515 (Box 5)
  - California Dreamin, 796514 (Box 5)
  - Candles for Girls, 796513 (Box 5)
  - The Candy Fun, 796512 (Box 5)
  - Candy Land, 796511 (Box 5)
  - Caprice, 796510 (Box 5)
  - Carbon and Carbide, 796509 (Box 5)
  - Cardboard Cutouts, 796508 (Box 5)
  - The Carnaval of Curious Urges, 796507 (Box 5)
  - Cartography for Beginners, 796506 (Box 5)
  - Cat's Claw Herbal, 796505 (Box 5)
  - Centering Home, 796504 (Box 5)
  - Chain Breaker, 796503 (Box 5)
  - Chameleon, 796502 (Box 5)
  - The Charming Deceiver, 796501 (Box 5)
  - Chelsea Kicks Ass!, 796500 (Box 5)
  - Cherry Blossom, Cherry Pie, 796499 (Box 5)
  - Cherry Cherry Red, 796498 (Box 5)
  - Chickfactor (2 Folders), 796497 (Box 5)
  - Child That Mind, 796496 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Chandler, 796495 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Halloween, 796494 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Sketchbook, 796493 (Box 6)
  - Chinese Sweatshop, 796492 (Box 6)
  - Chocoholic, 796491 (Box 6)
  - Choirgirl Powder, 796490 (Box 6)
  - Christmas Without Political Prisoners, 796489 (Box 6)
  - Chronicles of Disgust, 796488 (Box 6)
  - Cigarettes, Lips, These Fingertips, 796487 (Box 6)
  - Cigarettes and Pin-up Girls, 796486 (Box 6)
  - Circular, 796485 (Box 6)
  - Clarify Mission, 796484 (Box 6)
  - Cliterati, 796483 (Box 6)
  - Cliterature, 796482 (Box 6)
  - Cluck, 796481 (Box 6)
  - Clutch, 796480 (Box 6)
  - Cocktails: The TG Thinking Zine, 796479 (Box 6)
  - Coconut and Lime, 796478 (Box 6)
  - Cognitive Chaos, 796477 (Box 6)
  - Cognitive Mapping, 796476 (Box 6)
  - The Collected Void, 796475 (Box 6)
  - Comics and Zines Class Zines, Spring 2010, 796474 (Box 6)
  - The Compleat Mother, 796473 (Box 6)
  - Complete Control, 796472 (Box 6)
  - Continuum, 796471 (Box 7)
  - Cool Hand Zine Exchange, 796470 (Box 7)
  - Creative Garden, 796469 (Box 7)
  - Crimethlc Inc. Posters, 796468 (Box 7)
  - Critical Mass, 796467 (Box 7)
  - CROQ, 796466 (Box 7)
  - Crucial Sisterhood, 796465 (Box 7)
  - Crushed Angel, 796464 (Box 7)
  - Cultor-bore, 796463 (Box 7)
  - Cult Watch, 796462 (Box 7)
  - Cuntfear, 796461 (Box 7)
  - Cuntastic, 796460 (Box 7)
  - Cupcakes and Rainstorms, 796459 (Box 7)
  - Cubist Angels, 796458 (Box 7)
  - Cuddle Puddles and Hot Pants, 796457 (Box 7)
  - Culture Rag, 796456 (Box 7)
  - Culture Slut, 796455 (Box 7)
  - Cupcake or Death, 796454 (Box 7)
  - Cupcake Revelations, 796453 (Box 7)
  - Cyanide, 796452 (Box 7)
  - The Daily The, 796451 (Box 7)
  - Dames on Frames, 796450 (Box 8)
  - Dancesong Soul, 796449 (Box 8)
  - Dangeresque, 796448 (Box 8)
  - Dangerous Love, 796447 (Box 8)
  - Dara Larson Class Zines (Alverno College), 796446 (Box 8)
  - Deadlines, 796445 (Box 8)
  - Dead Stamp Collector, 796444 (Box 8)
  - Dear John, 796443 (Box 8)
  - Decoupage, 796442 (Box 8)
  - Demonstration, 796441 (Box 8)
  - Derangement/FUK, 796440 (Box 8)
  - Destroying Something Beautiful, 796439 (Box 8)
  - Diamond in the Rough, 796438 (Box 8)
  - Die, Evan Dando, Die, 796437 (Box 8)
  - Dildo, 796436 (Box 8)
  - Dirtybird, 796435 (Box 8)
  - Dirty Horror, 796434 (Box 8)
  - Dirty July, 796433 (Box 8)
  - Dirty Love and Fiberglass Smiles, 796432 (Box 8)
  - Dirtypop, 796431 (Box 8)
  - Discharge, 796430 (Box 8)
  - The Disgruntled Carpetbagger, 796429 (Box 8)
  - Digruntl TV, 796428 (Box 8)
  - Disheveled, 796427 (Box 8)
  - DIY Pet Care, 796426 (Box 8)
  - Do As I Say, Not As I Do: Family Lessons to Unlearn, 796425 (Box 8)
  - Doctrinal Expletives, 796424 (Box 8)
  - Dog Dayz, 796423 (Box 8)
  - "Don't Leave Your Friends Behind": Radical Parent Allies Handbook (2 Folders), 796422 (Box 9)
  - Don't Stop (Stop), 796421 (Box 9)
  - Doochisuck, 796420 (Box 9)
  - Doris (3 Folders), 796419 (Box 9)
  - Do You Support Mr. Lady Records? The Butchies? Le Tigre?, 796418 (Box 9)
  - Dracanea, 796417 (Box 9)
  - Dream Date, 796416 (Box 9)
  - A Dream Dies with Great Violence, 796415 (Box 9)
  - Dreaming of Oscar, 796414 (Box 9)
  - Driving Blind, 796413 (Box 9)
  - Drop Dead: a Zine of Lesbian Battering, 796412 (Box 9)
  - Dudes!: 13 Encounters, 796411 (Box 9)
  - Duplex Planet (2 Folders), 796410 (Box 9)
  - Edgy, 796408 (Box 10)
  - Elephant, 796407 (Box 10)
  - Elephant Shoe, 796406 (Box 10)
  - El Fanzineroso, 796405 (Box 10)
  - Emma Goldman (2 Folders), 796404 (Box 10)
  - Enraged, 796403 (Box 10)
  - Epiphany, 796402 (Box 10)
  - Eracism, 796401 (Box 10)
  - Erik and Laura-Marie Magazine (2 Folders), 796400 (Box 10)
  - E-Rot, 796399 (Box 10)
  - Escargot, 796398 (Box 10)
  - Esperanza, 796397 (Box 10)
  - Exploited Existence, 796396 (Box 10)
  - Express Stereo Scissor Boy and Glue Stick Girl, 796395 (Box 10)
  - External Text, 796394 (Box 10)
  - Eye of the Kudzu, 796393 (Box 10)
  - The E Zine, 796392 (Box 10)
  - Fabula, 796391 (Box 10)
  - Factsheet 5 (2 Folders), 796390 (Box 10)
  - Feminine Protection for Today's Woman, 796389 (Box 10)
  - Feminine Vengeance (2 Folders), 796388 (Box 10)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, 796387 (Box 11)
  - Feminists for Cleavage, 796386 (Box 11)
  - Femme Fatale, 796385 (Box 11)
  - Femmetopia, 796384 (Box 11)
  - Fertile Ground, 796383 (Box 11)
  - Fertility Awareness, 796382 (Box 11)
  - Festive, 796381 (Box 11)
  - Figure 8 (2 Folders), 796380 (Box 11)
  - Film Gofer's Digest, 796379 (Box 11)
  - Fire Down Below, 796378 (Box 11)
  - The Fire Inside, 796377 (Box 11)
  - The Firework Theory, 796376 (Box 11)
  - "The First 7-Inch was Better": How I Became an Ex-Punk, 796375 (Box 11)
  - First Song, 796374 (Box 11)
  - Flatter, 796373 (Box 11)
  - Fly Girl, 796372 (Box 11)
  - Flying Without Wings, 796371 (Box 11)
  - Fly Paper, Fly, 796370 (Box 11)
  - For My Sisters and the Burden We Share (2 Folders), 796369 (Box 11)
  - Found (2 Folders), 796368 (Box 11)
  - The Four Monkeys Review New York City Restaurants, or, Five Ripe Bananas, 796367 (Box 11)
  - France and Amber's Apartment, 796366 (Box 12)
  - Frat Boy Logic: A Continuation and an End, 796365 (Box 12)
  - Freegan Reich, 796364 (Box 12)
  - Free to Fight, 796363 (Box 12)
  - Free to Choose, 796362 (Box 12)
  - Friday...One Hour Til Quittin' Time, 796361 (Box 12)
  - From Here to There and Back Again, 796360 (Box 12)
  - Fuck Tooth, 796359 (Box 12)
  - Full Bloom Anon, 796358 (Box 12)
  - Full Tilt #2, 796357 (Box 12)
  - Fusion, 796356 (Box 12)
  - Future Fantasteek (2 Folders), 796355 (Box 12)
  - The Future Generation, 796354 (Box 12)
  - Fuzzy Heads are Better, 796353 (Box 12)
  - The F-Word (2 Folders), 796352 (Box 12)
  - Gambuzine, 796351 (Box 12)
  - The Game, 796350 (Box 12)
  - Gamine, 796349 (Box 12)
  - Gary Jones, 796348 (Box 12)
  - Geek the Girl, 796347 (Box 13)
  - Genderbent, 796346 (Box 13)
  - Genius Love, 796345 (Box 13)
  - A Gentrification Reader, 796344 (Box 13)
  - Getting Louder Everyday, 796343 (Box 13)
  - Giantess, 796342 (Box 13)
  - A Girl and Her Bike, 796341 (Box 13)
  - Girls are Not Chicks Coloring Book, 796340 (Box 13)
  - Girlcott, 796339 (Box 13)
  - GIRLcourage, 796338 (Box 13)
  - Girl Fiend, 796337 (Box 13)
  - Girlfrenzy, 796336 (Box 13)
  - Girl Noise, 796335 (Box 13)
  - Girl Swirl (2 Folders), 796334 (Box 13)
  - Girl Talk, 796333 (Box 13)
  - Girly Mag, 796332 (Box 13)
  - Gleaner Zine, 796331 (Box 13)
  - Global Backyards, 796330 (Box 13)
  - Give, 796329 (Box 13)
  - Glossolalia, 796328 (Box 13)
  - Goddess Juice, 796327 (Box 13)
  - GoGo Girl, 796326 (Box 13)
  - Good Times, 796325 (Box 13)
  - Good to Know, 796324 (Box 13)
  - Gorilla Wonders of the Diamon: A History Lesson, 796323 (Box 14)
  - Goth House Comics Collection 2, 796322 (Box 14)
  - Grandma Spike, 796321 (Box 14)
  - Greenwoman, 796320 (Box 14)
  - Greenzine, 796319 (Box 14)
  - Grrrl Style!, 796318 (Box 14)
  - The Gulper, 796317 (Box 14)
  - Gunk, 796316 (Box 14)
  - h2so4 (3 Folders), 796315 (Box 14)
  - Ha!, 796314 (Box 14)
  - Habit, 796313 (Box 14)
  - Hallowing of a House, 796312 (Box 14)
  - The Happy Loner, 796311 (Box 14)
  - The Happy Monger, 796310 (Box 14)
  - The Hardcore/Punk Guide to Christianity, 796309 (Box 14)
  - HardFemme Core, 796308 (Box 14)
  - Hard Knox, 796307 (Box 14)
  - Hatch! Mister Sister, 796306 (Box 15)
  - Heart Attack (2 Folders), 796305 (Box 15)
  - Heart to Heart: Exploring Yoga with Your Baby, 796304 (Box 15)
  - Heart vs. Brain, 796303 (Box 15)
  - Hearty Treat, 796302 (Box 15)
  - He, Her, Him: Free, Fer, Frim (2 Folders), 796301 (Box 15)
  - Hellraiser Homemaker, 796300 (Box 15)
  - Henry and Elizabeth, 796299 (Box 15)
  - Herbal Abortion, 796298 (Box 15)
  - Hermana, Resist, 796297 (Box 15)
  - Her Red Self, 796296 (Box 15)
  - Hier Babylon?, 796295 (Box 15)
  - High on Burning Photographs, 796294 (Box 15)
  - Hip Mama, 796293 (Box 15)
  - Hirsteria, 796292 (Box 15)
  - His World Her World, 796291 (Box 15)
  - Hit It or Quit It, 796290 (Box 15)
  - Hold Back a Glacier, 796289 (Box 15)
  - Hollow Daze, 796288 (Box 15)
  - Honeypot, 796287 (Box 15)
  - HotPantz, 796286 (Box 15)
  - How I Fell for Breakdancing, 796285 (Box 15)
  - How Judith Dench Went to Grad Schoool and What Befell Her There, 796284 (Box 15)
  - How the West was Won, 796283 (Box 16)
  - How to Survive High School from Someone Who Only Sorta Kinda Did, 796282 (Box 16)
  - hpv, 796281 (Box 16)
  - The Huge Underpants of Doom (2 Folders), 796280 (Box 16)
  - I Don't Like Mondays, 796279 (Box 16)
  - I Dreamed I was Assertive, 796278 (Box 16)
  - If I Could Live in Hope: Sexual Abuse and Survival, 796277 (Box 16)
  - I Hate Mom's Cat and Other Tails, 796276 (Box 16)
  - I Hate This Part of Texas, 796275 (Box 16)
  - I Hate You, 796274 (Box 16)
  - I Hear You Like Stories!, 796273 (Box 16)
  - The I in Feminism, 796272 (Box 16)
  - I Like Girls, 796271 (Box 16)
  - I Like It Thick, 796270 (Box 16)
  - An Illustrated Introduction to Booke Binding, 796269 (Box 16)
  - Ilse Content, 796268 (Box 16)
  - Imaginary Windows, 796267 (Box 16)
  - I'm Not Waiting, 796266 (Box 16)
  - Imperfect, 796265 (Box 16)
  - Infected Faggot Perspectives, 796264 (Box 16)
  - In Limbo, 796263 (Box 16)
  - In Morning Clouds, 796262 (Box 16)
  - Inner Bitch, 796261 (Box 16)
  - In or Out? Bisexuality and a Place to Call Home, 796260 (Box 16)
  - In Reference to Tuesdays, 796259 (Box 16)
  - insisterhood, 796258 (Box 16)
  - Instant Perspective, 796257 (Box 16)
  - An Introduction to Anarcha-Feminism, 796256 (Box 16)
  - Introvert (2 Folders), 796255 (Box 16)
  - Invincible Summer/Clutch, 796254 (Box 16)
  - The Invisibility of Women Prioners' Resistance, 796253 (Box 16)
  - Iron Femme, 796252 (Box 16)
  - I Should Have Seen It Coming, 796251 (Box 16)
  - I Spy (2 Folders), 796250 (Box 17)
  - Itch to Stitch, 796249 (Box 17)
  - It's Your Fucking Body, 796248 (Box 17)
  - I've Lost an Ocean, 796247 (Box 17)
  - I Want My Baby: the Miscarriage Zine, 796246 (Box 17)
  - Jane, 796245 (Box 17)
  - Jaundince, 796244 (Box 17)
  - Jodi Tilton: One of the Womyn the World Requires, 796243 (Box 17)
  - Journal Song, 796242 (Box 17)
  - Juliette's Zine, 796241 (Box 17)
  - Junglegym, 796240 (Box 17)
  - Junk/Food, 796239 (Box 17)
  - Junk Mail, 796238 (Box 17)
  - Junk Pirate, 796237 (Box 17)
  - Just Say No Thank You, 796236 (Box 17)
  - Just So You Know, 796235 (Box 17)
  - The Kaniksu Project, 796234 (Box 17)
  - Keep Loving Keep Fighting, 796233 (Box 17)
  - Ker-Bloom (2 Folders), 796232 (Box 17)
  - Kickstand, 796231 (Box 17)
  - Kitty Magik, 796230 (Box 17)
  - Koocachoo, 796229 (Box 17)
  - Kusp, 796228 (Box 17)
  - Ladders and Hips, 796227 (Box 17)
  - The La-La Theory, 796226 (Box 17)
  - Lamb's Lettuce, 796225 (Box 17)
  - Laundry Basket/Tales of Washday Woe, 796224 (Box 17)
  - Learning Good Consent, 796223 (Box 17)
  - Learning to Leave a Paper Trail, 796222 (Box 17)
  - Leeking Ink, 796221 (Box 17)
  - The Lesbian Lexicon Project, 796220 (Box 18)
  - Let It Be Known, 796219 (Box 18)
  - Let's D.I.Y. (2 Folders), 796218 (Box 18)
  - Let's Go to the Park, 796217 (Box 18)
  - Let Them Eat Cake!, 796216 (Box 18)
  - LGBTIQ Youth Resource Guide: Washington State, 796215 (Box 18)
  - Lick my Lit, 796214 (Box 18)
  - The Life and Times of Organic Farmers, 796213 (Box 18)
  - Life in a Glass House, 796212 (Box 18)
  - Lightningbug Zine, 796211 (Box 18)
  - Lilane in..., 796210 (Box 18)
  - Lily and Hyacinth Go to the Renaissance Faire, 796209 (Box 18)
  - Lily Liver (2 Folders), 796208 (Box 18)
  - Limousine/That Girl, 796207 (Box 18)
  - list (2 Folders), 796206 (Box 18)
  - Little Book o' Non Sequiturs, 796205 (Box 18)
  - Little Lady, 796204 (Box 18)
  - Little War Book, 796203 (Box 18)
  - Lollypop Shoved Up My Ass, 796202 (Box 18)
  - Lonely in a Magic Place, 796201 (Box 18)
  - Long Walk Back to Myself, 796200 (Box 18)
  - Look at My Hand, 796199 (Box 18)
  - Looking, 796198 (Box 18)
  - Loser Reflections, 796197 (Box 18)
  - Lost I.D./Feminist Women of Color Shout!, 796196 (Box 18)
  - Love is a Biohazard, 796195 (Box 18)
  - Love Letters to Monsters, 796194 (Box 18)
  - Love Like Pop, 796193 (Box 18)
  - Lovely Ugly Cruel World (2 Folders), 796192 (Box 18)
  - Love Shackles, 796191 (Box 18)
  - Loving for the Cause, 796190 (Box 18)
  - Lower East Side Librarian Winter Soltics Shout Out, 796189 (Box 19)
  - Low Hug!, 796188 (Box 19)
  - Low Motion, 796187 (Box 19)
  - Luna, 796186 (Box 19)
  - Luna Roja, 796185 (Box 19)
  - Lush: the A to Z Comp Zine, 796184 (Box 19)
  - Luxo, 796183 (Box 19)
  - Madame Henrouille, 796182 (Box 19)
  - Mad Love, 796181 (Box 19)
  - Madness, Motherhood, and Zines, 796180 (Box 19)
  - Malady, 796179 (Box 19)
  - Mamaphiles, 796178 (Box 19)
  - Mama Sez No War, 796177 (Box 19)
  - Mannequin Reject, 796176 (Box 19)
  - Manual of Co-operation (1885), 796175 (Box 19)
  - Mapping Cognitive, 796174 (Box 19)
  - Marika, 796173 (Box 19)
  - Marked for Life, 796172 (Box 19)
  - Master Bastion, 796171 (Box 19)
  - Masturbatory, 796170 (Box 19)
  - Maxine, 796169 (Box 19)
  - me., 796168 (Box 19)
  - Mental Potential and Sweet Emotions, 796167 (Box 19)
  - Merge Disorder, 796166 (Box 19)
  - Memoirs of a Queer Hapa, 796165 (Box 19)
  - Messy Baby/Messy Dog (2 Folders), 796164 (Box 19)
  - The Messy Eater, 796163 (Box 19)
  - MetaGirl, 796162 (Box 20)
  - Metasynderyne, 796161 (Box 20)
  - A Method of Reaching Extreme Altitudes, 796160 (Box 20)
  - Microcosm Publishing Catalog (3 Folders), 796159 (Box 20)
  - Mimsy Masing, 796158 (Box 20)
  - Mine: An Anthology of Women's Choice (2 Folders), 796157 (Box 20)
  - Minutiae, 796156 (Box 20)
  - Miranda, 796155 (Box 20)
  - Miranda Hearts Seattle, 796154 (Box 20)
  - Miso Horny!, 796153 (Box 20)
  - Misson 23, 796152 (Box 20)
  - Mistakes and Moving On, 796151 (Box 20)
  - Mister Fujiyama Loves You, 796150 (Box 20)
  - Mixtape, 796149 (Box 20)
  - Mmmph Zine, 796148 (Box 20)
  - Moan, 796147 (Box 20)
  - A Modern World, 796146 (Box 20)
  - Mohawk Pussy (2 Folders), 796145 (Box 20)
  - Mondo Beyond Comics, 796144 (Box 20)
  - Monkey Business, 796143 (Box 20)
  - Mons Venus, 796142 (Box 20)
  - Moon Tower, 796141 (Box 20)
  - Morgue Princess, 796140 (Box 20)
  - More Than Meets the Eye: Feminist Reflections on Party Culture at Duke, 796139 (Box 20)
  - Motomama, 796138 (Box 20)
  - Moxie, 796137 (Box 20)
  - Mr. Bunny Goes to Hollywood, 796136 (Box 20)
  - Mrs. Noggle, 796135 (Box 20)
  - Ms. Direction, 796134 (Box 20)
  - Multi-Kid, 796133 (Box 21)
  - Muppet in Training, 796132 (Box 21)
  - My Boat, 796131 (Box 21)
  - My Black Umbrella, 796130 (Box 21)
  - My Brightest Summer, 796129 (Box 21)
  - My Every Single Thing, 796128 (Box 21)
  - My Own Make-Believe, 796127 (Box 21)
  - My Paper Crane Zine, 796126 (Box 21)
  - My Silence was Golden, But Now It's Gone, 796125 (Box 21)
  - My Snow, 796124 (Box 21)
  - My Things, My Grandmother's Things, 796123 (Box 21)
  - Naked, 796122 (Box 21)
  - Nashville Femme, 796121 (Box 21)
  - Navigator Equator, 796120 (Box 21)
  - The Neighbors, 796119 (Box 21)
  - Nerve, 796118 (Box 21)
  - New Futur, 796117 (Box 21)
  - Neurotic Tendencies, 796116 (Box 21)
  - New to Everything, 796115 (Box 21)
  - The Next Body, 796114 (Box 21)
  - Next Phase, 796113 (Box 21)
  - No Better Voice, 796112 (Box 21)
  - Noisy Jewelry, 796111 (Box 21)
  - No More Secrets, No More Lies, 796110 (Box 21)
  - Noncollectable, 796109 (Box 21)
  - No Show, 796108 (Box 21)
  - Nothing on Earth is Big Enough to Crush My Beautiful Heart Poems, 796107 (Box 21)
  - Not My Small Diary, 796106 (Box 21)
  - Not Quite Israfel, 796105 (Box 21)
  - Not Sorry, 796104 (Box 21)
  - Not Without My Consent, 796103 (Box 21)
  - Not Your Mama's Cookbook (2 Folders), 796102 (Box 22)
  - Oblivion, 796101 (Box 22)
  - Obsolete, 796100 (Box 22)
  - Odd Girl Out, 796099 (Box 22)
  - OH, 796098 (Box 22)
  - Oh Dear!, 796097 (Box 22)
  - Oh January, 796096 (Box 22)
  - Old Weird America, 796095 (Box 22)
  - Once Were Warriors, 796094 (Box 22)
  - On Edge, 796093 (Box 22)
  - One Night Stand, 796092 (Box 22)
  - On the Table: My Sexual Assaults, 796091 (Box 22)
  - On Zines: North Carolina, 796090 (Box 22)
  - Open All the Time, 796089 (Box 22)
  - Oppositional Defiance, 796088 (Box 22)
  - Orange Shoes, 796087 (Box 22)
  - Orange Vanilla Treat, 796086 (Box 22)
  - The Order of the Sacred Hippopotami, 796085 (Box 22)
  - Other Ramona, 796084 (Box 22)
  - Out of the Closets and Into the Libraries, 796083 (Box 22)
  - Outpunk, 796082 (Box 22)
  - Own Your Own Yoni, 796081 (Box 22)
  - Oz!, 796080 (Box 22)
  - Paper Crush, 796079 (Box 22)
  - Papercutter, 796078 (Box 22)
  - Paper Doll (2 Folders), 796077 (Box 22)
  - Parents in Prison, 796076 (Box 22)
  - Parthenogenesis, 796075 (Box 22)
  - Passion in Public, 796074 (Box 22)
  - Patina, 796073 (Box 22)
  - Patriarchy Kills, 796072 (Box 22)
  - Pauline, 796071 (Box 22)
  - PDX Zines, 796070 (Box 22)
  - The Peak, 796069 (Box 23)
  - Pecola Breedlove, 796068 (Box 23)
  - Penelope and Transexual Fairytale, 796067 (Box 23)
  - Peoples, 796066 (Box 23)
  - The Period Conspiracy, 796065 (Box 23)
  - Permed, 796064 (Box 23)
  - Persephone is Pissed, 796063 (Box 23)
  - Petty Hearts/Sincere Lies, 796062 (Box 23)
  - Phases of the Moon (3 Folders), 796061 (Box 23)
  - Philly Love Zine, 796060 (Box 23)
  - The Pine Box, 796059 (Box 23)
  - Pink Tea, 796058 (Box 23)
  - Pipu, 796057 (Box 23)
  - Pity Party, 796056 (Box 23)
  - Plague Project, 796055 (Box 23)
  - Planet 3.9, 796054 (Box 23)
  - Planet Girl, 796053 (Box 23)
  - The Plastic Tower, 796052 (Box 23)
  - Playing Stickball on Company Time, 796051 (Box 23)
  - Please to Meet You, 796050 (Box 23)
  - The Pleiades, 796049 (Box 23)
  - Plotz (2 Folders), 796048 (Box 23)
  - Polar Bears Luv, 796047 (Box 24)
  - Pomegranate, 796046 (Box 24)
  - Pony Express Zine, 796045 (Box 24)
  - Pop Boffin, 796044 (Box 24)
  - Popcore, 796043 (Box 24)